在此读书，我们将谈论的规格。
In this reading, we'll talk about specifications.
说明的是像一个合同
A specification is like a contract
你计划的一部分，说什么可以指望
for part of your program, saying what it can count on
从程序的休息和什么
from the rest of the program and what
它的预期回报的事情。
it's expected to do in return.
规格与所有三个帮
Specifications help with all three
这course--安全漏洞，从大的目标，
of the big goals of this course-- safety from bugs,
容易理解，并准备变革。
ease of understanding, and readiness for change.
这个阅读后，你应该
After this reading, you should be
能够理解方法的前提条件和后置条件
able to understand preconditions and post-conditions in method
规格，能够写出正确的规格，
specifications, be able to write correct specifications,
你应该能够编写测试
you should be able to write tests
针对本说明书中，你应该
against this specification, you should
知道之间的差别检查，未经检查
know the difference between checked and unchecked
例外的Java，你也应该
exceptions in Java, and you should
了解如何使用特殊效果异常
understand how to use exceptions for special results
从的方法。
from a method.
OK，让我们开始吧。
OK, let's get started.